Guide to the Federal Theatre Project photograph collection, 1936-1939
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 1: Production Photographs, 1936-1939; (84 boxes)
  - Trois Bon Amis -- French Unit (Los Angeles, California), January 13, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Trois Bon Amis -- French Unit (Los Angeles, California), January 13, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Trojan Incident (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Trojan Incident, 1930s (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Trojan Incident, 1930s (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Truck containing props, 1930s (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Turn to the Right (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Turn to the Right (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Turn to the Right (San Diego, California), July 21, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Turn to the Right (San Diego, California), July 21, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Turpentine (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Turpentine (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Turpentine -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Turpentine -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Turpentine -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Turpentine, 1930s (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Tweedles (Oakland, California), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Tweedles (Oakland, California), June 12, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Tweedles (Oakland, California), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Twelfth Night (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Twelfth Night (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Twelfth Night (Jacksonville, Florida), January 13, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Twelfth Night (Miami, Florida), March 29, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Twelfth Night (Miami, Florida), March 29, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Twelfth Night (Miami, Florida), March 29, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Two A Day (Los Angeles, California), October 28, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Two A Day -- Vaudeville (Los Angeles, California), October 28, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Two A Day (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Two A Day (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Two A Day (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Two A Day (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - The Two Hundred Thousand -- Yiddish (Boston, Massachusetts), December 6, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - The Two Hundred Thousand -- Yiddish (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - The Two Hundred Thousand -- Yiddish (Boston, Massachusetts), December 6, 1938 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Two Hundred Were Chosen (Peoria, Illinois), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin -- Marionette (Los Angeles, California), April 23, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin -- Marionette (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Jacksonville, Florida), April 11 - 29, 1939 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Springfield, Illinois), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Buffalo, New York), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin -- Marionette, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Uncle Vanya (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Uncle Vanya (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Uncle Vanya (Los Angeles, California), December 8, 1936 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Uncle Vanya (Los Angeles, California), December 8, 1936 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Undertow (Bronx, New York), 1930s (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Unidentified -- Backstage, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified -- Behind the Scenes, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Unidentified photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified group photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Unidentified group photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified negatives, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified photographs, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified photograph of a bust, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Unidentified photograph of a bust, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified productions (Chicago), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified productions (Chicago), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified productions (many different plays), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified productions and sets, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified productions (O'Neill players), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified productions (Chicago), May 4, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified productions, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 20)
    Banquo and Fleance. "How goes the night, boy."
  - Unidentified set, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified set, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified set, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Unit 1-B, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Unto Such Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Unto Such Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Unto Such Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Up Pops the Devil (San Diego, California), November 7, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Up Pops the Devil (San Diego, California), November 7, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Up Pops the Devil (San Diego, California), November 7, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Up Pops the Devil (San Diego, California), November 7, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Up Pops the Devil (Peoria, Illinois), 1936 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Uriel Acosta (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Uriel Acosta (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Uriel Acosta (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Various Productions (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Various Productions (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Various Productions, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Various Productions: Marionettes and Dance and Magazine, 1930s (Box 94, Folder 23)
    Materials are included for the magazine Broadway "PIC" and the publication Federal Theatre: "Men Against Microbes" (Boston, MA.), "Crocodile" (Phila, PA.), "William Brodie" (Des Moines, Iowa), "Big Blow" (Chicago Federal Theatre 1939), "The Crock of Gold" (San Francisco, California), "The World We Live In" (Los Angeles, California), "Altars of Steel" (Miami, Fla.), "The Weavers" (Los Angeles, California), "Little Black Sambo" (Chicago, Illinois), "Hansel and Gretel" (Los Angeles, California).
  - Vaudeville (San Francisco, California), September 1, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Vaudeville (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Vaudeville (San Francisco, California), January 1 - 30, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Vaudeville (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Vaudeville (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Vaudeville (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Vaudeville (Syracuse, New York), May 16, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Vaudeville (Washington, D.C.), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Vaudeville (Washington, D.C.), 1930s (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Vaudeville, 1930s (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Vaudeville, 1930s (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Vaudeville, 1930s (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Vaudeville Frolics (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Vaudeville Revue (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - The Very Great Man (San Diego, California), September 21, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - The Very Great Man (San Diego, California), September 21, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - The Very Great Man (San Diego, California), September 21, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Volpone (Los Angeles, California), December 28, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Volpone (Los Angeles, California), December 28, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Volpone (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Walk Together Chillun' -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Walk Together Chillun' -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Walkins, Perry (Haiti), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Walkins, Perry, 1930s (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Los Angeles, California), 1936 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - The Warrior's Husband (San Francisco, California), October 17 - 18, 1937 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - The Warrior's Husband (San Francisco, California), October 17 - 18, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Denver, Colorado), October 1, 1937 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - The Warrior's Husband (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Watson, Morris -- Power (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Watson, Morris (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Watson, Morris (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - We Live and Laugh -- Yiddish (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - We Live and Laugh -- Yiddish (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - The Weavers (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - The Weavers (Los Angeles, California), November 23, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - The Weavers (Los Angeles, California), November 23, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - The Weavers (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Wedding Bells (Syracuse, New York), May 30, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Wedding Present, November 6 - 7, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - What a Woman Wants (San Diego, California), June 8, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - What a Woman Wants (San Diego, California), June 8, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - What a Woman Wants (San Diego, California), June 8 - 9, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - What Anne Brought Home (Los Angeles, California), November 20, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - What Anne Brought Home (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - What Anne Brought Home (Los Angeles, California), November 20, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - When Husbands Meet (Syracuse, New York), April 24, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - When Knighthood Was In Flower (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - When Knighthood Was In Flower (Jacksonville, Florida), October 12, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - When Knighthood Was In Flower (Jacksonville, Florida), October 12, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Whistling in the Dark (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Whistling in the Dark (San Diego, California), July 7, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Whistling in the Dark (San Diego, California), July 7, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Whistling in the Dark (New Orleans, Louisiana), October 14, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Whistling in the Dark (Salem, Massachusetts), January 27, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Whistling in the Dark (Salem, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - The Whole Town's Talking (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - The Whole Town's Talking, 1930s (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Whom Dreams Possess (Miami, Florida), April 12, 1939 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Whose Cat (Washington, D.C.), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Why Men Leave Home (Los Angeles, California), April 18, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Why Men Leave Home (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Why Men Leave Home (Illinois), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Why Men Leave Home (Illinois), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Wild Birds (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Will Shakespeare (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Will Shakespeare (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Will Shakespeare (Los Angeles, California), May 20, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Will Shakespeare (Los Angeles, California), May 20, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (Los Angeles, California), March 2, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (Los Angeles, California), March 2, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (San Diego, California), May 11, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (San Diego, California), May 11, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (San Diego, California), May 11 - 12, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - The Wisdom Tooth (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - With My Red Fires (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Within These Walls (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Within These Walls (New Orleans, Louisiana), April 10, 1939 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - A Woman of Destiny (Bronx, New York), 1936 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - A Woman of Destiny (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Workshop -- Children's Theatre (New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Workshop -- Costumes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Workshop -- Costumes, 1930s (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Workshop -- Make-up, 1930s (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Workshop -- Make-up, 1930s (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Workshop -- Set Design, Costume Design, Lighting Tech (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Workshop -- Props (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - World's Fair (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - World Trip (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - World Trip (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - The World We Live In (Los Angeles, California), August 20, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - The World We Live In (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - The World We Live In (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - The World We Live In (Los Angeles, California), September 27 - 29, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - The World We Live In (Los Angeles, California), September 27 - 29, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - The World We Live In (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - The World We Live In (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Yankel Boyla (Los Angeles, California), May 12, 1938 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Yankel Boyla (Los Angeles, California), May 12, 1938 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Yankel Boyla (Brooklyn, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Yankel Boyla (Brooklyn, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Young Choreographer's Laboratory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Young Choreographer's Laboratory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Young Choreographers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Young People of Town of Falling Waters, 1930s (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Young Tramps (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Young Tramps (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Young Tramps (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Your Uncle Dudly (Manchester, New Hampshire), 1930s; (82 boxes) (Box 82, Folder 36)
- Series 2: Oversize Production Photographs, 1936-1939; (6 boxes)
  This series is comprised of photographs relating to productions, including scene shots, stage and set shots, and portraits. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 83 to 88. The series is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city, or by subject. This series includes oversize duplicates from photographs contained in series one and series three.
  - Altars of Steel (Birmingham, Alabama), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Another Language (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Anthony and Anna (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - As Husbands Go (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Audience -- Children, 1930s (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - The Barker (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Bassa Moona (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Big Blow (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Big Blow (Chicago, Illinois) (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - The Big City -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - The Big White Fog (Chicago, Illinois), April 6, 1938 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Birds (Roslyn, New York), September 1938 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Brass Trumpet -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Broken Dishes (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Captain Jinks of the Horse Marines (Roslyn, New York), August 26 - 28, 1937 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - The Case of Philip Lawrence (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Circus -- African Warriors, 1930s (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Circus -- Clowns, 1930s (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Circus -- In the ring, 1930s (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Community Theatre (New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - The Copperhead (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Conjur Man Dies (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Coriolanus (Roslyn, New York), November 1937 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - The Cricket on the Hearth (San Francisco, California), December 1937 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Devils Disciple, November 25, 1937 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - The Devil Passes (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - The Devil Passes (San Francisco, California), December 22, 1936 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Diff'rent (Roslyn, New York), November 24, 1937 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - The Dragon Snee Zee -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Eternal Prodical (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - The First Mrs. Fraser (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - The Fool (Berkeley, California), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Fresh Fields (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Fresh Fields (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - The Good Fairy (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - The Good Old Summertime (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - The Good Old Summertime (New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - The Great Barrington (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Help Yourself (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Her Majesty the Widow (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - I Want a Policeman (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - How Long Brethren (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - If Ye Break Faith (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Injunction Granted (New York City, New York), July 1936 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Invitation to a Murder (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - It Can't Happen Here (Buffalo, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - It's a Wise Child (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Lady Say Yes (San Francisco, California), May 1 - 16, 1936 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - The Late Christopher Bean (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - The Lonely Man (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Macbeth (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Marionettes -- Vaudeville (San Francisco, California), April, August 1937 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Mary Stuart (Los Angeles, California), April 29, 1936 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - The Mikado -- Swing (Chicago, Illinois), 1938 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Mister Jim (Chicago, Illinois), July 8, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Nineteen Thirty-Five (1935) (New York City, New York), May 1936 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - No More Peace (Roslyn, New York), June 17, 1937 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - No More Peace (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - No More Peace, 1930s (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Noah (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - The Old Maid (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Oliver Twist (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - On Top (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Path of Flowers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Personal Appearance (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Pirates of Penzance (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - The Playboy of the Western World (Roslyn, New York), January 12, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Possession (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Post Road (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Post Road (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Power (San Francisco, California), July 28 - August 19, 1937 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Prologue to Glory (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Prologue to Glory (New York City, New York), May 1939 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Rip Van Winkle (Buffalo, New York), 1936 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Secret Service, 1936 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - See Naples and Die (Chicago, Illinois), December 29, 1938 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Showing Off (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - The Straw (Chicago, Illinois), October 26 - December 18, 1937 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Street Scene (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Sun Up (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Tailor Becomes a Store Keeper, February 25, 1938 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Tamed and How (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Tea for Three (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Terrible Meek (Elmhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 87, Folder 16)